

PROFILE

9 years of web developing experience for multiple domains including business, healthcare, ecommerce, etc.

Blockchain developer with 4 years of experience for Dapps, NFT, Defi projects etc.

Excellent coding and testing ability ensuring optimal functionality, quality, and reliability.

LINK

website

CONTACT

Address:

1132 Granada Street, Fort Pierce, Florida, United States

PHONE:

(805) 214-8119

FMAII .

phillipgrandi89@gmail.com

LANGUGAE

English

HOBBIES

Football Piano

PHILLIP GRANDINETTI

Full Stack Engineer 7 years Web Developer 9 years Blockchain Developer 4 years

EDUCATION

University of Virginia

August 2008 - May 2013

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science

WORK EXPERIENCE

Chainalysis Inc (Full Stack Developer)

February 2020 - July 2022

- Built Web projects using React.js, AWS, Vue.js, Node.js, Web3.js and Ether.js according to requirements and development guidelines.
- Implemented robust, scalable, quick, efficient, well-designed software that is easy to maintain and test.
- Tested software security using tools like burp suite and kali linux, and wrote clean, well-documented code.

SoluLab (Software Developer)

July 2018 - February 2020

- Built various kinds of web projects and ML tools using Javascript and Python frameworks.
- Developed clean, tested smart contracts with Solidity using Remix and Hardhat and deployed them on Ethereum networks.

Kortek Solutions (Full Stack Developer)

October 2015 - July 2018

- Created flexible and scalable applications that help commerce companies improve their operations.
- Developed business projects using React.js, Vue.js and Node.js as business services.
- Built features in a full range of applications and services
- Optimized site code for speed and resiliency.

Modea (Junior Web Developer)

May 2013 - October 2015

- Developed healthcare web application frontends using React.js, Redux and Vue.js.
- Implemented new user-facing features and built reusable components using React.js and Vue.js.

SKILLS

